(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
Help!
Help, please!
Guys, I think we’re almost there.
Almost?
After we've walked all this way!
We're already so exhausted!
Look at Dave!
He's been quiet for a while.
Is he still alive?
Dave's just a quiet guy!
He's an introvert, remember? Introvert!
Dave!
Are you still okay?
Sorry guys.
I was just being careful.
There might be snakes around the area.
Didn't you think of that?
You'll be fine! Just
walk on the tall grass.
[alarm beeping]
What's that?
Where is that coming from?
Step count!
10k steps already.
Matt, seriously?
Thank you, bro!
This isn't the time for that!
Sorry, my bad.
But don't forget, it's intrams next month.
Got to get my steps in, bro!
Guys, wait!
Are you sure this is the right way?
Wow!
I never pegged you as a complainer, Zein.
You've always liked these kinds of things.
Because when I make the plans,
I use GPS not a rusty old map!
This map is legit!
If that's legit, where did you find it?
Just trust me.
Trust you?
Boo!
Shit!
Relax, girl. Why are you
such a scaredy cat today?
Nice one!
It's so hot!
Let's go!
Come on.
She's worrying about nothing.
Be careful.
It's so steep!
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
Where are we going?
Wow! The almighty Zein Shion gets scared?
The Zein Shion.
What are you talking about?
Do you remember when you
punched someone who catcalled you?
That Zein Shion.
First of all...
that was a roundhouse kick, not a punch.
Second, wow.
How did you even remember that?
Of course, I remember.
Besides, you were known for that back then.
Didn't you get suspended because of that?
How would I know that
punk was a nosebleeder?
Was it worth it?
If you could go back to the past
and change things, would you?
As if!
Shit!
If anyone tries to hurt
you again, don't worry.
They're gonna have to go through me first
before they can have a
taste of your roundhouse kick.
Wow, thanks.
Guys!
How long 'til we get to Hell Academy?
Hell University!
Sounds like a horror film!
Guys, wait!
This place looks so creepy!
If this is a horror film, I'm claiming it.
I'm going to be the final girl.
FYI.
Sure, as long as I'm the comic relief
who doesn't die early.
You know...
I think the annoying
cheerleader would suit you more.
The nerve...
you're the only annoying one here.
Guys...
I did my research.
I can't find any schools
in the gps or maps.
Are you sure about this, Mia?
This school is abandoned.
But according to my map
we should be close to the gate.
You mean that gate?
Is anybody inside?
Hell University.
Guys...
do you think we can ask for
some drinking water?
I'm so thirsty.
I left my water tumbler at home.
Unless, she's willing to share.
You wish!
No way!
Nice try, boy.
I have a bad feeling about this, guys.
Maybe we should go back?
Huh?
After all that?
We've walked so far!
Mia's right.
We've come all this way.
Let's check first if
they'll accommodate us.
There's no one inside!
Is anyone there?
Jerome, you're too loud!
- Hello?!
- Jeez.
Anyone!?
Jerome!
Guys, let's leave while
there's still sunlight!
Come on!
Jer, what's wrong with you?
There's someone there.
What are you doing here?
Sir...
are you the caretaker here?
How did you find this place?
We got lost while hiking, sir.
Then we found this school.
We thought it was abandoned.
We’ve run out of water...
Would it be okay to ask for some inside?
Do you want to come in?
But this should be clear...
this place isn't abandoned.
You mean there are students inside?
Oh, there you go!
Come on, Zein!
You kept complaining earlier.
Now you're quiet? Are you okay?
Right.
Don't tell me you're a
scaredy cat now, Zein Shion?
Stop teasing, Zein.
She's just tired.
It's okay, Zein. We'll be fine.
We should move before it gets dark.
You're right.
Let's go?
Okay.
There are doors... that once they close...
You’re not the same when you come out.
If you even come out.
There, we'll go to the admin office.
Remember...
This university changes at 7:00 p.m.
Be careful.
You all need to register.
Register?
Like an attendance, sir?
We're just lost, we're
not planning to enroll.
Why not?
Isn't it cool?
Think of it this way...
even if we cut class in this school,
they won't tell our parents.
Jerome doesn't make sense
most of the time, but I agree.
Guys, stop playing around.
We're here to stock up supplies
then we're leaving.
Guys!
Stay close.
- What's happening? They're being weird.
- Guys...
Go back to your dorm.
Students, come on!
Shit!
- Oh my god! This is crazy!
- Let's stick together!
What are you looking at?
What's happening?
- I don’t like this place, let's go home!
- Sir!
Sir! We want to go back!
Go back to your dorms!
What?
This is your fault, Mia!
What kind of map was that?
Is this really a school?
What the hell is happening?
Let's go back home.
Stay close, guys.
Are they following us?
I want to go home!
Guys!
I told you so!
Sir, we'll go back!
Guys...
What's going on?
They have weapons!
- Stay close, guys.
- What's happening!
What do you want?
Stay away from me!
What's going on?
What are they doing?
Stay together!
What's happening?
It's just a riot.
Don't mind them.
Riot?
Why is no one stopping them?
Your questions will be
answered inside. Let's go!
No... we'll go home!
I don’t like this!
We want to go home!
Don’t panic!
What’s happening?!
Guys, faster!
Oh my god.
You know,
I'm starting to get why this
place is called Hell University.
This place is just so out of the box.
And their approach to
education is... unique.
Unique? You call that riot unique?
Are you being serious, guys?
Am I the only one who
saw that riot outside?
We all did, Zein.
I don't care anymore!
I only want to know if this place has WiFi.
Oh my god...
we soiled their floors.
It's okay, maybe they have janitors here.
Come on, guys.
He's leaving us.
Are you with the admin?
Where are we going?
We're going to the headmistress' office.
She can explain the registration process.
We're not going to enroll.
Do you think we would want to after
witnessing what's out there?
Dave, look.
He looks like a doctor slash cult leader.
Jerome, stop it! Let's go.
Stop saying nonsense!
Am I right?
What did we get ourselves into?
What if something bad happens to us?
Calm down, we'll get out of here safe.
Hello, newbies.
I am Madam Violet.
Headmistress of Hell University.
Simply put...
I'm in charge around here.
Madam Violet.
No offense...
But are you aware of
the riot going on outside?
Don't fret.
It happens all the time.
Francisco...
Have them fill these out please.
How much is the tuition fee here?
There is no tuition fee.
Everything is free.
Is this a public university?
No.
We're private.
It's complicated.
Let's just say that we are not
your conventional university.
Conventional?
What do you mean?
7 pm to 5 am is what we call Freedom Night.
Also known as Bloody Night.
Everything is free.
You are free to do whatever you want.
Killing is allowed.
So I suggest that you stay in your rooms...
Lock up your doors,
and don't go out.
Because if you step outside...
You may not come back alive.
Wait a minute.
Are you serious?
You're spewing nonsense!
Nonsense...
But it seems cool!
- Cool?
- Cool.
This is insane!
Guys, let's leave. The
people here are crazy.
Zein...
Guys?
This is the adventure we've
been looking for, isn't it?
Just agree, Zein.
Zein, let's listen to her first.
Maybe this will be good for us.
Let's give it a try.
If we can't handle it, we'll go home.
Let's stay for one night.
Right! And we don't have
anywhere else to stay the night.
It's more dangerous outside.
What are you so afraid of, Zein?
I'm not afraid!
Then it's settled.
Francisco, can you take
them to their rooms, please?
Fear is not a liability.
So if I were you, Miss?
Zein.
Zein Shion.
Miss Zein.
It’s a good thing you’re scared.
Because fear is something
you would need here to survive.
Be careful!
Even your friends cannot be trusted.
Never let your guard down.
Or else...
If you know what I mean.
The directions to you
dorms are in the packets.
You live in one dorm: separate
rooms for girls and boys.
The instructions are in the packets.
At least it's like a sleepover every day?
And everything is free. Even our dorms.
Not bad. Slay!
Welcome to Hell University.
If we enroll here, we'll be dormmates.
It's spacious. Not bad.
Slay!
Guys, where are the rooms?
I don’t know.
I think it's over here.
Come on, let's check!
Okay.
This is nice!
Let's use this room!
And for the girls?
Let's use this room, right?
Matt.
Check in with Zein.
Go to her.
Zein...
Zein, are you okay?
I just miss my sister.
Allison.
Zein...
Why don't we give it a chance?
Look...
It seems nice here.
The dorm is free.
Even the tuition.
Matt...
What are saying? Aren't you a scholar?
Not for long.
I got kicked out of the team, Zein.
I don't even know how to tell my parents.
Matt...
Sorry.
I didn't know.
That's okay.
But please don't mention
it to the others yet.
It's embarrassing.
There's something
wrong with this place, Matt.
What Violet said isn't normal.
Killing is legal?
What kind of school does that?
Maybe it's just a scare tactic?
I think it's best to follow their rules for
now and think about the rest tomorrow.
Are you really scared?
Is it because of the riot?
Don't worry.
Nothing bad is going to happen to you.
Or all of us.
You're the bravest girl I know.
Remember during elementary,
when our classmate made fun of me?
Before I could do anything,
you already kicked him.
But I got scared too when
he was about to retaliate.
Good thing you had my back.
I was surprised you were
willing to take a punch for me.
Of course I would.
It's you.
I won't let anything bad happen to you.
and Mia and Vanessa.
The boys are big enough
to handle themselves.
So for now...
Let's just rest.
Let's worry about the things
we have to deal with tomorrow.
Do you want me to walk you to your room?
No, it's okay.
I just need some air.
Look out for them, okay?
I’ll just take a walk.
Alright.
Matt...
Matt!
What?
Jerome took your spot.
He said you can sleep on the floor.
What a nutcase.
I'll deal with that first.
Get some rest, Zein.
Okay.
- Good night.
Hell University...
I thought my old school
was already a hellhole.
Where are the students?
Why is it so quiet?
You're bleeding!
Are you okay?
That's not my blood.
What's your name, newbie?
Zein.
Angel-like but I know
you'll use a knife soon to survive.
Scared?
You shouldn't have come here.
Who are you?
I'm not a friend.
No one is your friend.
I'll let you free for now, newbie.
It's already 6:30 pm. You
still have thirty minutes.
Lock all the doors.
All eyes are on you and your friends.
Watch your back.
- Sorry, bro.
- What?
There's no other pillows left.
That's my pillow.
Bro, give this to me.
Please? I'm so stressed out.
Fine.
I'm sorry, bro.
How are you able to
workout in this situation?
Aren't you scared?
I'm scared.
Really scared.
For my future...
My decision to enroll here...
My parents...
Who are worried about me now.
I still don't know.
How to tell them.
But when I'm moving...
My mind stops spiraling.
I think much clearer.
I'm my family's disappointment.
So I'm sure they're not worried about me.
"Jerome? He always gets home late."
"He's probably just partying."
"Drinking himself to death."
Story of my life.
They're looking for you.
All our parents are worried about us.
Don't spiral, bro.
We'll tell them to let us out tomorrow.
Do you think Madam
Violet is telling the truth?
That killing is legal during Bloody Night?
Seriously?
You're falling for that?
Maybe she was just using it
as a metaphor or something?
You know, a discipline tactic for students.
You're overthinking it.
Relax.
No, I feel like she's saying it literally.
Whatever.
Van?
What's that?
That’s Vanessa!
I don't know. Let's check it out.
Let's go!
Van?
Van!
What's wrong?
This is so frustrating!
There's no WiFi! No signal!
What's wrong with this place?
Van...
I need to call mom and dad
for sure they're worried about me.
Let's try asking the students tomorrow.
Maybe they have a way
to contact the outside?
Tomorrow!?
I can't last that long.
My followers are waiting for me!
Van, how did you fit all these in there?
Of course!
Beauty is essential.
At least if I die, I'm
going to die beautiful!
Bloody Night, bring it on!
This is so frustrating!
Wait, where's Zein?
Zein?
She was just here earlier.
Guys...
Zein!
Are you okay?
There's a boy in the park...
wearing a mask...
his shirt was bloody.
He warned me!
We made a mistake...
This is no longer fun!
Maybe he was just pranking you?
He wasn't.
Zein, worrying will kill you first.
No!
Is it Bloody Night already?
Shit!
Over here!
Run faster!
Faster!
Help me, please!
Open the door! Help him!
Please, let's help him!
Open this! I'll kill you all!
Get in! Quick!
One...
Two...
Three!
Bring it up!
What's happening?
What's wrong with this place?
I don't want to die!
Guys, don't give up!
- I'm going to kill you all!
- We can do this!
I'm going to kill you all!
Guys, I don't want to die.
Boys! Let's get out of here.
Are you all okay?
So that’s all you’ve got?
Dave, are you okay?
Yeah, I’m okay.
Are you guys okay?
Guys, I don't want to die in this place.
Please...
Let's leave this place, please!
Let's stick together no matter what.
( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
Dave's right.
When daylight comes...
Let's ask for help from the admin.
I see that you're back at my office.
Good morning, Madam Violet.
We want to leave this place!
Why? What's the problem?
This university is a complete mess!
Why isn't the government
doing anything about it?
Watch it, Ms. Zein Shion.
This university is independent
from the government.
They can't touch us.
We're going to leave
this shithole of a school!
We have rules here...
Once you enter...
there's no turning back.
What do you mean?
We're not kidding around here. Let us go!
No.
You entered this place on your own accord.
Live with the consequences.
Bullshit!
We're going to leave this place!
And we'll make sure to
report you to the police!
Go ahead, Mr. Jerome Marquez.
Find a way out.
If you can find one.
Nobody's stopping you.
Now I have a very busy day
so if you're done yapping around...
I suggest
wear your uniforms and go to your classes.
Excuse me?
Are we still going to study?
Will we learn anything in
this place besides killing?
Hell University is still a school.
The teachers here are
the cream of the crop.
They are the best.
You will learn a lot from them
compared to other schools.
Wow!
I can't believe teachers apply
here with all this happening.
Amazing!
I wouldn't worry about them.
Think of it this way...
their salaries aren't normal either.
Sometimes they get paid double...
triple...
You know what, that’s enough!
If I were you...
get changed to your
uniforms and go to class.
Cause if the President
gets a hold of you...
the consequences are unimaginable.
We need to leave.
My mom and dad...
they're looking for me!
Are we really going to be able to leave?
Mia.
In... out, okay?
Look at me.
Five counts.
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Five.
Relax.
Newbies!
So the rumors are right.
Six rats have entered this place.
Let me give you a tip
if someone tries to bring you down...
cut their arm off.
Cause in this place...
kindness is luxury
and survival is currency.
Sometimes even rats
eat each other to survive.
So if I were you...
it's better to move alone.
Hey!
Don't worry about us.
We're leaving this place.
Leave?
Do you think you can
still leave this place?
Go ahead.
Show me the way out when you find one.
Why?
You don't know the way out either?
Didn't they tell you?
Once you enter
there's no turning back.
Welcome to Hell University...
newbies.
I couldn't go outside from the chaos.
Were you there?
I wasn't.
Everyone got knocked out.
You didn't leave?
- It was almost a bloodbath.
- No. I'll go out later.
Wait for me later, I'll show them.
Excuse me.
Excuse me...
Who are these new students?
Yeah.
I don't recognize them.
How did they enter this place?
Good luck!
Do you like manga?
Sorry... it's just that
you're good at drawing.
Good morning, class!
You thought you were safe?
Good morning, class.
I see we have new students here.
Why don't you introduce yourselves?
Zein Shion.
Jerome Marquez.
Promise
I'll behave...
for now.
You think you're cute, huh?
Hey, hey, hey!
Settle down!
Settle down, class!
May I have your attention, please.
The elixir of immortality.
There are many rulers
who are willing to kill
to find the elixir that stops death.
Like I've said, the elixir of immortality.
Many have died in search for this.
It's been ages but no one has succeeded.
After a while, the myth of
the elixir has been forgotten.
In the event
that you find
the elixir of immortality.
What will you do with it?
[woman screaming]
What was that?
What's happening?
Don't go out!
Zein, let's go!
Is that Mia?
Jerome, it's Mia!
Who did this?
The Black Blood Gang attacked again.
That nail in his tongue...
is their symbol.
They showed up again
after the events last week.
This only means one thing...
another war will happen soon.
And I know this war will be bloodier
now that they've killed Raze
Silvenia's one and only brother.
Raze Silvenia?
The leader of the Devil God Warrior.
Devil God Warrior?
Black Blood Gang?
Who are they?
The two most powerful gangs in this school.
Stay away from them.
Especially during Bloody Night.
All students!
Go back to you classrooms!
Now!
What happened?
Who is that?
Do you know everything?
I said...
If I want to know something...
I'll figure it out on my own.
You've got some nerve, huh?
Guys, Zein is missing!
Where is she?
She told us to meet her here.
Speaking of Bloody Night...
so what's the plan?
Are we going to lock
ourselves in the dorms again?
For how long are we going to hide
when the clock strikes 7:00 p.m?
Zein, it’s 7:00 p.m.
Shit!
There's this girl...
I heard from some students.
That she's hard headed and reckless.
Keep an eye on her.
Boo!
Don't you have classes?
What are you doing here?
Who are you?
Ace Craige.
The Supreme Student Government
President of Hell University.